sunnysidesoft.com 2017-06-25

# SUNNYSIDESOFT| Privacy Statement

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SunnysideSoft collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the VirtualTablet application (“App”). This privacy policy applies to the App offered by SunnysideSoft.

**1\. Personal/Non-personal identification information**

We do not require any identification information from Users at all.  
Names and IP addresses of computer which are nearby User can be automatically or manually collected but will not be stored in locally or remotely using Internet.  
**2\. How we protect your information**

The information which is sent/received through the network does not include any personal identification information. It only contains the movement, pressure and button click input data from stylus pen.  
**3\. Changes to this privacy policy**

SunnysideSoft has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our App. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**4\. Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this App, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our App. Your continued use of the App following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.  
**5\. Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this App, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
SunnysideSoft  
www.sunnysidesoft.com

This document was last updated on November 12, 2012
